FRANCISCO BRUNO DA SILVA SOUSA, 25

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

I'm a full-stack developer, with more than 1 year and a half of experience in web development. I have solid knowledge in functional programming and in the main front-end technologies, such as Bootstrap, Angular, Jquery, Javascript, React and CSS preprocessors. I am interested in working on frontend applications, applying my knowledge in scalable projects and with the best development practices.

CONTAC

Celular: +55 85 99437 4607 E-mail: brnsadv@gmail.com

Fortaleza - CE - Brazil

SOCIAL MEDIA*

*Icons are clickable







FLUENCY

ENGLISH LEVEL B2 | INTERMEDIATE

TECHNOLOGIES I USE

ADVANCED HTML

ADVANCED CSS

ADVANCED SASS

ADVANCED BOOTSTRAP

ADVANCED JAVASCRIPT

INTERMEDIARY JQUERY

INTERMEDIARY NODE.JS

INTERMEDIARY NESTJS

INTERMEDIARY EXPRESS
INTERMEDIARY FIREBASE

THE BY SE

ADVANCED ANGULAR

INTERMEDIARY REACT

INTERMEDIARY VUEJS

INTERMEDIARY MYSQL

INTERMEDIARY PRISMA

INTERMEDIARY RECTNATIVE

INTERMEDIARY DART

INTERMEDIARY FLUTTER

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

JUNIOR DEVELOPER III

Sunne Energias Renováveis | Jan 2023 - present

• Unit testing using jasmine and karma, code review, and building the design system.

JUNIOR DEVELOPER II

Sunne Energias Renováveis | Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

 I'm responsible for designing and developing user interfaces, writing clean, efficient and well-optimized code. In addition, I seek to ensure high performance in desktop and mobile applications.

HEAD OF MARKETING | COMMUNITY MANAGER

Barreto e Maia advogados | Julho 2019 - Julho 2021

 Responsible for taking care of all communication at BMadv, carrying out marketing campaigns with Adobe design tools, producing document layouts, institutional presentations, as well as managing its community, in addition to maintaining relationships with important people.

LEGAL INTERN

Barreto e Maia advogados | Janeiro 2019 - Julho 2019

RELATIONSHIP COORDINATOR

Federação das Empresas Juniores do Ceará - FEJECE | Jan 2018 - Jan 2019

• Responsible for managing FEJECE's actions with its partners, in addition to articulating the Federation's relationship with the main agents of the 1st, 2nd and 3rd sector.

PERSONAL AND PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Adobe Package (Illustrator and Photoshop)
Active Listening
Organization
Team management
Time and team management
Fast learning
Office pack
Social Media Strategy and web
content development
Project management
Communication/Speech
Market research

OTHER CERTIFICATIONS

Training in Web Designer by Gracom School of Visual Effects Certificate in Data for Business Advanced course in Community Manager by Distrito for startups.

MÍDIAS SOCIAIS*

*Os ícones são clicáveis







ACADEMIC EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

CENTRO UNIVERSITÁRIO UNIFANOR WYDEN | Julho 2020 - Present

LAW GRADUATION

Centro Universitário 7 de setembro | Agosto 2017 - Agosto 2022

- 100% scholarship holder of the University for All program (PROUNI);
- Participation in study groups on legal innovation, visual law and legal design;
- Foundation of the Junior Law Firm.

ADDITIONAL TRAINING

BOOTCAMP: FULL STACK DEVELOPER + ANGULAR

SoulCode Academy | Setembro 2021 - Janeiro 2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPER + PYTHON

Escola Britânica de Artes Criativa | Setembro 2021- Janeiro 2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

ProgramadorBR | Junho 2021- Janeiro 2022